ecigadvanced.com 2018-02-23

# Privacy Policy – Electronic Cigarette News

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site through the [Forums](http://www.ecigadvanced.com/forums), [Vape For Free](http://www.ecigadvanced.com/rewards/) or subscribe to our newsletter.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you will be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address and sometimes mailing address. You may visit our site anonymously by not completing the registration process.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (Showing content and information that is relevant to your account and account preferences)
  * To improve our website (We continually improve our website and features based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)
  * To improve site functionality (Your information helps us to effectively make sure EcigAdvanced.com is bug-free.)
  * To send an occasional email (The email address you provide for your account, will only be used to send you information on e-cigarette news, giveaways and more, **if** you subscribed to our newsletter. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving newsletters or emails,  we’ve included  unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.)

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you register for the site, place an order in Vape For Free or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

**Do we use cookies?**  
EcigAdvanced.com uses cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser, capture and remember certain non-private information

We use cookies primarily to serve specific advertisements to you based on your location and past activity on EcigAdvanced.com through our partner ad network, [Ecigmedia.](http://www.ecigmedia.com/) These advertisements may be shown to you on EcigAdvanced.com, or other websites where Ecigmedia advertisements are shown.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential with the same respect to privacy as we outline here. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy as we do our own, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. Ever.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to ‘User Account’ in our Forums or ‘My Account’ in Vape For Free.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older (actually 18, but this part is specifically related to COPPA).

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 3/19/2013

Did you find apk for android? You can find new [Free Android Games](https://dlandroid24.com/) and apps.
